

Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City, VietName

□ (+84) 868374742 | ☑ nvtanh.dev@gmail.com | ☑ https://github.com/nvtanhh | 🛅 https://www.linkedin.com/in/nvtanh

Summary

Currently working at a France outsourcing company. Mobile Developer with experience in designing, developing, and maintaining mobile applications. I am enthusiastic about mobile development and aim to become a full-stack mobile developer. Passionate about bringing ideas to life, thinking out better problem-solving for challenging tasks, and willing to learn new technologies.

Skills

Programing Dart · Flutter · Docker · Firebase · Hasura (GraphQL) · MySQL · NodeJs · MongoDB

Tool Git · Trello · Redmine · Figma · Adobe XD · ClickUp UI/UX designing · Presentation · English communication

Work Experience _____

FAVIE TECH. HCMC, Vietnam

MOBILE DEVELOPER · (FLUTTER)

Mar. 2022 - Present

- · Worked in an Agile environment and experienced using ClickUp a project management tool · Ability to work on multiple projects and deliver them on time
- Directly work with stakeholders to clarify requirements and raise ideas
- Experienced working with crypto applications
- Experienced working with advanced animation
- Experienced working with AWS Cognito

Dolphin Solutions JSC.

MOBILE DEVELOPER · (FLUTTER) Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2022

- Android: https://bit.ly/3FsGVyj | iOS: https://apple.co/33iHddR
- Develop Okuro app (a social network app specialized for education)
- Implemented features: News Feed, Create post, Comment, Search, Chat,... Migrating app to Flutter 2.0
- Working closely with colleagues to develop, and maintain app functionality
- Participate in the functional analysis / UI design of some features in the system
- Responsible for release testing/production versions on both Android and iOS
- · Working familiar with widgets, basic animation, Provider, Stream, Bloc, Socket.io, Storage,... in Flutter

Personal Projects_

SOCIAL NETWORK FOR PET · WOOFIE

Dissertation

Feb. 2021 - Aug. 2021

HCMC, Vietnam

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER · UI/UX

- Android: https://bit.ly/3JcfSLf (not maintained) Demo: https://bit.ly/3J9x1Uh
- Description: Woofie is a specialized social network app for pet and pet lovers
- Team size: 2
- · Features:
 - · Social network basic features: news feed, create a new post, push notification, comment (real-time), explore, chat (attach: image, video,
 - Manage pet profile with health records and reminder
 - Support finding your pets a new family or adopting them
 - Tinder for pet help they find a partner
 - SOS alert "Lost Mode" an extremely useful feature to find a losing pet
- Tech stack:
 - Client: (App & Web) Flutter, GetX, TDD Clean Architecture
 - Social Network Service: GraphQL (Hasura), Go, Postgres
 - Chat Service: Node.Js, Express, MongoDB, Socket.IO Source: https://bit.ly/3vv4LYb
 - 3rd Party services: Firebase Authentication, MinIO (object storage server), One Signal
 - Deployment: Docker, Docker-Compose, Linux, GitHub Actions CI/CD

TANH NGUYEN · RÉSUMÉ MARCH 18, 2023

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER · UI/UX

Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- · Android: https://bit.ly/3fE4gCN
- Description: This application is a tool to help Vietnamese rappers easy to find rhymes based on a given word and help them write and manage songs, and records song
- · Features:
 - Authentication with Facebook and Google
 - Find rhymes based on given word Favorite rhythms list
 - Find the meaning of the word (crawling live data from another dictionary website
 - Song management, record, and play song demo
- · Tech stack:
 - Flutter
 - Back-end: Python/ Flask (for finding rhymes API); Firebase (for authentication, songs management)
 - · Deployment: Heroku

Education

Nong Lam University

HCMC, Vietnam

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Sep. 2017 - Sep. 2021

- GPA: 3.4/4.0
- Agriculture and Forest University Student of the Year for 3 consecutive years

Honors & Awards _____

HONORS

Oct. 2021	Nong Lam University Student of the Year (2020-2021)
Oct. 2020	Nong Lam University Student of the Year (2019-2020)
Nov. 2020	KMS Grants Scholarships for information technology students at HCM
Oct. 2019	Nong Lam University Student of the Year (2018-2019)

AWARDS

Nov. 2020 First Prize, 3rd Scientific Research Ideas

Nong Lam University

Extracurricular Activity

Greentea Club (An academic club at the Faculty of Information Technology)

Nong Lam University
Feb. 2019 - Oct. 2021

EADER

Support the faculty to organize academic and surgical activities

- · Organize programming classes for members and students in the faculty to help them improve their programming skills
- Organize useful programs for Nong Lam University students such as: "Free Windows installation", "Laptop Buying Guide"

March 18, 2023 Tanh Nguyen · Résumé